marianos.com 2017-02-23

# privacy policy

**Roundy's Supermarkets, Inc. Online Privacy Statement   **

Roundy's Supermarkets, Inc. (â€œRoundy'sâ€) respects your concern for online privacy and has adopted the following Online Privacy Statement. This Statement explains the online data collection and disclosure policies and practices of Roundy's websites including: PicknSave.com, Copps.com, MetroMarket.net, Marianos.com, and Roundys.com (collectively, the â€œRoundy's Sitesâ€). Your use of any of the Roundy's Sites indicates your acceptance of this Statement. If you do not consent to this Statement, please immediately cease using any of the Roundy's Sites. We reserve the right, at any time, to modify this Privacy Statement.

**Visitor and Session Tracking  
**Roundy's tracks the total number of visitors to our Sites allowing for proper administration and improvements. Cookies (pieces of data stored in your hardware) are used to track information including browser type, operating system, IP address, and domain names, as well as logged in status, store selection, and other non-personally identifiable selections, in order to provide a customized experience. Some functionality within the Sites will not work properly if your browser does not accept cookies.

**Information Provided by You  
**We provide you with the opportunity to register for an account within each of the Roundyâ€™s Sites. Within your account profile(s), you may choose to provide us with your name, contact information, store selection, Rewards Card number, and dietary/nutrition preferences. This information is used to give you a personalized website experience, including displaying the ad for the store of your choice and showing you specials based on your past purchase behavior.

You may also find entry forms or surveys within our Sites, or the ability to change information relating to a Rewards Card. Roundyâ€™s will only collect personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide through a Roundyâ€™s Site or email.

We may request that you voluntarily submit personal information such as your name, address, email address, phone number, Rewards Card number, and store selection if you attempt to contact the Roundyâ€™s Customer Service Center via one of the Roundyâ€™s Sites. You may also voluntarily make submissions to Roundyâ€™s. We have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information except as provided in this Statement. We use such information internally for the purposes collected, and we treat any comments, suggestions and the like as public information.

Roundyâ€™s has the right to access your account at any time for the purposes of Customer Service Support.

If you would prefer that Roundy's not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any information. We do not share this information with outside parties; however, Roundy's may disclose personally identifiable and aggregate anonymous information to companies and individuals employed to perform functions on our behalf (such as contest or promotion administration) or with our affiliates, partners or parent company. These companies and individuals may have access to your personal information to perform their business functions on our behalf as well as their own business purposes such as assisting us in administering various promotions and providing specific promotional offers to you. Roundy's will provide those other companies with the information they need to perform the services and, except in the case of contests and promotions administered by outside companies, we prohibit them from using the information for other purposes. We do not control how other companies use the information you may provide directly to them (such as pursuant to a contest registration) and recommend that you check the privacy statement of the company requesting information for a description of their data collection practices. Please be aware that subsidiaries and affiliates of Roundy's are not outside parties or outside companies, and we may periodically share personal information or aggregated information with Roundy's subsidiaries and affiliates.

**Email  
**When an email address is given by a visitor indicating inclusion in a Roundy's subscription list, we will send notices to the visitor in the form of an email. You may opt-out of this subscription at any time by updating your profile. Please [Sign In](http://www.marianos.com/Profile/SignIn.aspx), click on 'My Account' and uncheck Weekly Email.

**Passwords and Security  
**You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any passwords and restricting access to your accounts. You accept responsibility for all activities that occur within your account or with your password.

**Third Party Websites  
**The Roundy's Sites may contain links to or iframes of other websites over which we have no control. These websites include but are not limited to our Careers/Application portals for job seekers, Pharmacy prescription refill and pet medications ordering sites, Investor Relations site, FuelRewards.com, SavingStar.com, UPromise.com, CouponNetwork.com, and others. Roundy's is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you may link to or view from a Roundy's Site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of such websites so that you can understand how those companies collect, use, and share your information. This Statement applies solely to the information that Roundy's collects on the Roundy's Sites and does not apply to information Roundy's may collect by any alternative means or media such as at stores owned by Roundy's.

**Pharmacy Notice of Privacy Practices  
**While our Pharmacy prescription and pet medication portals displayed within the Roundyâ€™s Sites are hosted and managed by external companies, and therefore information gathered and managed by those companies are subject to those companiesâ€™ privacy policies, they do have a Pharmacy notice of privacy practices that can be viewed [ **here** ](https://www.carehealth.me/PrivacyPractices/).

**Personal Information We Collect From Other Sources  
**We may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand, and analyze our records and identify new customers.

**How to Change Your Information  
**If you have submitted personally identifiable information through a Roundyâ€™s Site and would like to change that information, please [Sign In](http://www.marianos.com/Profile/SignIn.aspx) and click on 'My Account'. 

**Security Measures  
**Roundy's has instituted various procedures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, ensure the correct use of information, and safeguard and secure the information we collect about you. However, Roundy's cannot guarantee that unauthorized access or disclosure of information will never occur. Roundyâ€™s reserves the right to terminate your account, change your password, or request information to authorize actions within your account as we deem necessary or reasonable to ensure security.

**Children's Privacy  
**Roundy's Sites do not collect or maintain information at our Sites from those we actually know are under the age of 13. From time to time, we may display information that is specifically aimed at children, for example coloring pages. However, registration is never required to access these pages, and we do not collect personal information in connection with these activities.

**Wireless Marketing Services  
**Roundyâ€™s may invite you to register to receive alerts, promotions, services, news, and other information (each a "Wireless Marketing Service") via text messaging and other wireless devices such as mobile phones. Such Wireless Marketing Services are provided by Roundyâ€™s and/or its contractors or vendors for Roundyâ€™s. Wireless Marketing Services are limited to adult subscribers who reside in the United States and are void where prohibited.

If you wish to receive a Wireless Marketing Service, you must expressly consent to receive that Wireless Marketing Service from Roundyâ€™s.

_Availability._ In order to receive Wireless Marketing Services, you generally must have a text messaging service plan from a participating wireless service provider. Our Wireless Marketing Services may not be available in all geographic areas or work on all mobile or wireless devices. Mobile devices that can receive text messages (SMS Service) are generally able to receive text alerts. You agree that Roundyâ€™s will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any Wireless Marketing Services or related messages, as delivery depends on the effective transmission from your carrier or network operator. Please contact your wireless provider if you have questions regarding your SMS service.

_Personal Information._ The personal information requested as part of the registration process may include a user's telephone number, a wireless email address or the carrier's name. Additional information may be requested for specific Wireless Marketing Services, such as a user's preferences regarding goods or services, or other similar information. Subject to applicable law, we may use this personal Information in accordance with our Online Privacy Statement.

_Security/Delivery._ You should keep in mind that most wireless transmissions are not secured. There is a greater risk that an unauthorized third party may intercept your messages or your personal information when you use a wireless communications device. Therefore, if you choose to sign up for any Wireless Marketing Services, you agree that Roundyâ€™s will not be liable to you for damages caused by a third party's interception of such items.

_Potential Charges._ Roundyâ€™s does not charge users for its Wireless Marketing Services. However, your carrier's standard message and data rates may apply. Charges may show up on your mobile bill or may be deducted from your prepaid account. By registering to receive Wireless Marketing Services, you agree that you may be charged by your wireless carrier for any messages that you send to or receive from Roundyâ€™s and that you are solely responsible for such charges. Under no circumstances will Roundyâ€™s be responsible for any wireless email or text messaging charges, whether incurred by you directly or as a result of the activity of another person with access, whether or not authorized, to your wireless device, telephone number, or email address. Please contact your wireless carrier if you have any questions about your wireless service.

**How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals**   
If you have enabled your Internet browser to refuse cookies or have selected a "do not track" preference, we will not collect personal information about you. In addition, when you visit our website, third parties will not collect personal information about you or your online activies over time or across websites.

**Online Advertising**   
Information collected by our advertising service providers through cookies and other technologies may include browsing behavior, referring sites and your response to advertisements. These cookies do not collect personal information. Data collected in this manner is only used to improve our advertising.

Roundy's Supermarkets, Inc. participates in the [AdChoices online behavioral advertising program](http://youradchoices.com/) (http://youradchoices.com/). If you receive a behaviorally targeted advertisement, you may click on the displayed icon to receive more information and choose to opt out. Your opt-out choices may be affected by your use of a specific device, your browser settings or your log-on credentials. If you opt out, you may still receive online advertising from Roundy's Supermarkets, Inc. which is not based on your preferences or online behavior.

**Browsers**   
We may collect certain information form your browser, such as your media access control (MAC) address, device type, screen resolution, operating system version and Internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that our websites function properly and also for security reasons.

**Location Tracking**   
We may collect information about your physical location through our websites and mobile applications. An example includes your physical location when you search for a nearby financial advisor using your mobile device.

Â© 2012 Roundyâ€™s Supermarkets, Inc. All Rights Reserved.

**Roundy's Supermarkets, Inc. Online Terms of Use**

The following websites: PicknSave.com, Copps.com, MetroMarket.net, Marianos.com, and Roundys.com (collectively, the â€œRoundy's Sitesâ€) are made available to you by Roundyâ€™s Supermarkets, Inc. (â€œRoundyâ€™sâ€) for the purposes of finding store locations, planning shopping trips, and learning about the practices and operations of Roundyâ€™s stores. By using the Roundyâ€™s Sites, you are entering a binding agreement between you and Roundyâ€™s. Roundyâ€™s reserves the right, at any time, to modify these Terms of Use.

**Privacy  
**Please review our Privacy Statement, which also governs your visit to the Roundyâ€™s Sites.

**Ownership  
**The Roundyâ€™s Sites and all Roundyâ€™s electronic communications, in their entirety, including but not limited to all design and content, are the sole property of Roundyâ€™s Supermarkets, Inc. and its content partners and is protected by United States and international copyright, trademark, and other laws. Except as stated, no content may be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed, posted, or transmitted in any form or by any means without the prior written consent of Roundyâ€™s or the respective owner. You may not use Roundyâ€™s or its banners names, logos, or other trademarks for any purposes without the express written consent of Roundyâ€™s. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by Roundyâ€™s.

**Submissions  
**All submissions, including suggestions, comments, original creative stories, messages, product ideas, artwork, text, graphics, video content, audio content, photos, or other, will be and remain the exclusive property of Roundyâ€™s. Roundyâ€™s will be entitled to use, reproduce, disclose, publish, and distribute any submissions for any purpose whatsoever, without restriction and without compensating you in any way.

**Copyright Policy  
**Roundyâ€™s does not permit copyright infringing activities on the Roundyâ€™s Sites. Roundyâ€™s abides by the federal Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") by responding to notices of alleged infringement that comply with the DMCA and other applicable laws. As part of our response, we will remove materials if properly notified that such materials infringe on another's intellectual property rights.

**Electronic Communications  
**When you visit the Roundyâ€™s Sites or send emails or text messages to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically so that we may respond to your communications. We will communicate with you by email or by posting notices on the Roundyâ€™s Sites, and you agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures, and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

**Conduct and Site Security  
**Any conduct by you that, in our sole discretion, restricts, inhibits, or interferes with the ability of any other person to use or enjoy the Roundyâ€™s Sites will not be permitted. The Roundyâ€™s Sites may only be used for lawful purposes. You are prohibited from (a) accessing or using the Roundyâ€™s Sites in order to collect information about Roundyâ€™s Sites visitors or registered users of Roundyâ€™s Sites, (b) violating or attempting to violate the security of Roundyâ€™s Sites, or (c) using any device, software, or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Roundyâ€™s Sites or any activity being conducted on the Sites. Violations of system or network security may result in civil or criminal liability.

You acknowledge and agree that Roundyâ€™s may, in its sole discretion and without liability to any person, terminate or modify any or all elements of the Roundyâ€™s Sites, email programs or Wireless Marketing Services at any time without notice. In its sole discretion, Roundyâ€™s may announce changes on the Roundyâ€™s Site or elsewhere.

**Links  
**You may create text-only hyperlinks to our Sites. You are not permitted to use a link that "frames" the Roundyâ€™s Sites or that portrays Roundyâ€™s, its store banners, or its products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory, or otherwise offensive manner. Also, you may not use any Roundyâ€™s logo, graphic, or trademark as part of the link without our express written permission.

**Monitoring  
**Roundyâ€™s reserves the right, but not the obligation, to monitor areas of the Roundyâ€™s Sites electronically and to remove information and materials that Roundyâ€™s deems, in its sole discretion, to be objectionable. Roundyâ€™s expressly disclaims any obligation or warranty to screen or remove objectionable materials. Roundyâ€™s further reserves the right to disclose any content, records, or electronic communication of any kind if we are required to do so by any law, regulation, or court order, or if such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to operate the Roundyâ€™s Sites or to protect Roundyâ€™s rights or property, or the rights of the other Roundyâ€™s Sites users, or our partners, affiliates, sponsors, providers, licensors, or merchants.

**Third Party and Co-branded Sites  
**Roundyâ€™s may provide links or iframes on the Roundyâ€™s Sites to other websites (including co-branded websites) that are not under the control of Roundyâ€™s. Roundyâ€™s does not assume any responsibility for the operation, content, privacy practices of such websites, or the technology they implement. You agree that you use these websites at your sole risk. Roundyâ€™s in its sole discretion may modify or remove such links at any time and without notice.

**Disclaimers  
**Although Roundyâ€™s reserves the right to correct any errors, omissions, or inaccuracies, you acknowledge that the information on the Roundyâ€™s Sites are provided â€œas is,â€ without representations or warranties of any kind and that your use of the Roundyâ€™s Sites is at your own risk. Roundyâ€™s does not warrant that the Roundyâ€™s Sites or any information, content, or services offered through the Roundyâ€™s Sites, or any electronic communications sent from Roundyâ€™s, are free of viruses or other harmful components.

**Limitation of Liability  
**You agree that Roundyâ€™s and its affiliates will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of the Roundyâ€™s Sites or any information, content, or services offered through the Sites, unless otherwise specified in writing.

**Indemnities  
**You agree to hold harmless Roundyâ€™s and its respective shareholders, officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, and suppliers from any and all claims arising out of or related to your access or use of the Roundyâ€™s Sites or your inability to access or to use the Roundyâ€™s Sites or from any services rendered by Roundyâ€™s or its contractors in conjunction with the Roundyâ€™s Sites or your use of the Roundyâ€™s Sites.

**Applicable Law  
**By visiting the Roundyâ€™s Sites, you agree that the laws of the State of Wisconsin, without regard to principles of conflict of laws, will govern these Terms of Use and any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Roundyâ€™s.

**No Waiver  
**Roundyâ€™s failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.

Â© 2012 Roundyâ€™s Supermarkets, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
